Hello.
I'm Akira Koike from the Kura Taka legal family home.
I'm Yoshin Fujiyoshi.
I've just arrived at Shin-Osaka.
Yay!
Today, following the Miyazaki Koukan
We are going to visit this restaurant
We are going to Osaka to eat delicious gourmet food together!
I'm off!
First time traveling with Nakai-chan!
It's not often that two people do something together.
It's my first time.
What's this?
Here and a joke.
The one with the four jokes in it.
It's delicious.
Osaka Castle? Is that...
What is it?
Oh, it's cool.
I couldn't get a shot of it. It was too flashy.
Where is he going now?
We're on our way to a TV taping.
Mr. Beginning Television.
Yes, I'm here.
I'm going to go to the taping now.
I'm going to work.
I'm on the terrace of
Terrace
I'm here to see you.
Look at this spectacular view!
Osaka Castle Hall
Osaka Castle Park
You can also see Osaka Castle.
Osaka...oh!
I can see it.
When the cherry blossoms come...
Around here.
I heard the cherry blossoms will be in full bloom.
I wish I could have come to see them.
Maybe then.
Please come and see for yourselves.
Instead of us.
Spring
I tried.
Do you have something you want to do?
With Ehime home
I want to see cherry blossoms
I've only seen fallen cherry blossoms
I've never seen them in full bloom.
Cherry blossoms in full bloom
I want to see cherry blossoms
I want to enjoy them with you.
I'd like to enjoy them with you.
That's nice.
The other day...
I went on a trip by myself.
In the spring.
I wonder if I'll be able to see more beautiful scenery.
I wonder if I can go to Osaka Castle
I wonder if I can go to
When you joined us.
When you joined us, did you have this impression of us?
Like children and adults.
We were so young.
And the older members...
They're so sophisticated.
That's why we can sing this kind of music
I think it's because of them
I think it's because they are the ones who can sing
in a good way.
So in a good way
There is a mysterious atmosphere
I'm pretty good at it.
It's the same now.
I really like your performance.
You've said that from the beginning.
Ever since we danced together.
I've been thinking about it.
You've always said so.
You've even written about it in magazines.
It's true.
I love how natural you are.
I want to
want to tell everyone.
I think everyone knows this.
There it is.
I'll cut it off with my head.
It's exquisitely hidden in the tree.
But you put it on anyway.
That's great.
Thank you very much for watching.
Welcome to Tsutingu Tower
We're here!
We've arrived!
Everything is fresh!Everything is fresh.
A town that feels like Osaka
Streetscape
Ta-da!
Newly added Iri-ken products!
Made in Iri-ken
This is definitely scary!
This is terrible!
It's quite transparent.
That's scary.
It's scary, isn't it?
Oh, it's really scary. Really scary.
Quick, where did you go?
Don't stop.
I'm really scared. I'm really scared.
I really can't look down. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
That was fun.
It was amazing.
It was scary.
I was really scared.
Was there one that wasn't there?
We have arrived.
After this, we will be on the music bit.
Yes, I will. I'll do my best.
I am Minami Koike from Sakura High School 46.
I'm Fujiyoshi Karin. I look forward to working with you.
I'm Minami Koike, and I'm Yoshikazu Fujiyoshi.
Actually, Ms. Koike is from Hyogo and Ms. Fujiyoshi is from Osaka.
So we are both from Kansai.
We are friends.
I guess that's the end of today's work.
We're done. What are you going to do now?
Okonomiyaki.
Yay!
We can have dinner at night.
Let's make love.
What do you mean?
I'm on a roll today, Koike-san.
Why?
You're so cool.
I came to buy okonomiyaki.
They're here.
Look, bonito worms are dancing.
That's great.
Let's get a good shot of this.
Yay! It's done!
Here's the okonomiyaki.
This is Romance's okonomiyaki.
This is the Romance cheese.
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Delicious, Raffa.
It's rich.
Yes, it is.
It's just like Osaka, isn't it?
Romance cheese.
Sorry.
I'm mixing up my feelings.
I'm very sorry.
It's delicious.
Thank you for the food.
I'm not hungry.
But I can still have dessert.
We have dessert today, so from now on.
It's Pettak.
I think I like you now.
Do you think so?
Yes, I do.
I'll try.
Here he comes.
Wow, that's not good.
That's not good.
Maybe it's still like a mon grass fit.
Ichizenzo three.
One forward three?
I guess.
About the single.
It's a sad feeling that I can understand.
It's like a painful feeling.
Do you think it's your first challenge?
I wonder how it will turn out.
I'm not sure how it will turn out, but I think it will be a cool coupling.
It was a music video that went beyond animation, wasn't it?
That was also interesting.
I thought Oizono was wonderful.
I thought she was wonderful.
It's a stone of love.
This is badass.
My favorite store.
Really.
You said earlier that you missed it.
I really miss it.
We didn't meet before I became a supervisor.
It's not that I met him before I became a supervisor, but after I became a supervisor, I came back.
I started going to this restaurant.
Hee...
Yes, ma'am.Yes, ma'am.
Yes, please.
It's delicious.
Is it good?
Is that what you always eat?
It's good.
I usually have it.
Matcha green tea within matcha green tea within matcha green tea.
It's thick.
Very thick.
It's called "mont blanc".
It's all matcha.
So thick!
It's not good, is it?
It's not good.
It's matcha.
It's so matcha.
Delicious!
I'm home.
I was able to visit many places today.
I was very happy to be able to go around with Karin.
It was fun.
It was fun. Coming to Osaka.
We ate a lot of delicious food.
It was good. I came to talk with you. It was fun.
It was fun.
It was Pirate South and
Shibuya Shikabayashi.
Thank you very much.
Was it too loose?
Vlog. Bye-bye.
Bye bye.